Thanks for joining us everybody. Just a
reminder for the
joint press conference to state name and
affiliation and who the question is
directed at.
All right, good to see you
[clears throat] guys. Um,
as we're getting rolling, I think as the
season's over, a lot of you would say,
all right, now what? And for AP and I,
uh, we would say, man, it's just the
beginning. We got a lot of work to do.
And I know you'll
uh, ask, you know,
what changes are, you know, being made
and uh, we're not able to go there yet.
Everything needs to be and is being
uh, thoroughly
examined and discussed and uh,
really our work is answering the
question, what went wrong and what do we
need to do to fix it? And uh,
make sure we never, you know, go through
this again. And a season like this. And
so, that's our sole focus and and what's
kind of going to be driving us, you
know, in the weeks ahead. So, just
wanted to
kick it into that in gear with you. I
know AP will hit a few things and then
we'll get the whole thing rocking.
Yeah, just to echo what DQ said. I mean,
this season was, um, a disappointment in
a lot of ways and certainly didn't meet
our standards and, um, you know, we're
going to do everything we can to not let
that happen again and and that starts
today with this off season. So,
ready to attack it and and ready to move
forward and, um, whenever you guys are
ready, go ahead and hit us with some
questions. John Keim with ESPN for both
of you.
You don't know about the changes, but
when would you like to get those
finalized? And what goes when you're
going about assessing coaches,
coordinators, what how do you go about
assessing them to get to whatever
decision you want? Yeah, for sure. It's,
uh, after a hard season like this, hard
decisions are made, but you want to go
through,
uh, everything from
evaluation, the communication, the
performances. And so, we begin that,
um,
as coaches and the coaches and scouts,
we get together, we talk a lot about the
players. We had the exit interviews
today, John. So, Adam and I also visited
with a lot of players and that's part of
how we're, you know, gathering all of
our information. So, all of these
processes are really important and
we just want to make sure like we're
doing everything we can, you know, to
make sure we're hitting all the marks to
to get it right.
And Adam, for you, since we haven't
talked to you in a little while, want to
go back to the summer with Terry and
given how the season played out for
Terry, the injuries, the early struggles
and all that, how would you assess how
that situation was handled and how can
you apply whatever you learned to future
situations? Yeah, certainly. Um,
I think, uh, I think both, uh, us and
Terry would agree that we would like to
get that done a little bit faster. It
didn't happen that way.
Um, certainly, you know, um,
you know, that that, you know, there's
reasons for that, but, um, ultimately
you'd like to get those things done
before we did. Um, in terms of where
Terry's at, uh, I thought, you know,
obviously he got hurt early, but I
thought he did a really good job at the
end of the year. I was really pleased
with where he's at. Playing at a really
high level right now and going into next
year. So,
really pleased with the end result of
the contract. Obviously, you'd like to
get it done earlier and I think it's a
good lesson, too, just, um, just
engaging in those things a little bit
earlier and hopefully you get to the
um, to the to the end before we did on
this one and certainly we'll we'll do
that moving forward.
Um, Nicki Jhabvala with The Athletic.
Um,
just for both of you. Um, just looking
back over this past season, how would
you assess the work that Cliff did with
the offense? Yeah, we're going through
all of all the the coaches, um, Cliff
offensively, defensively, on the teams
wide. So,
um, that's really what we're digging
into, Nicki, to find what's best, how do
we do it, you know, where do we find
spaces to improve? And, um, you know,
for Cliff, for Joe, for Larry, for all
of us, like that's our main focus, like
so we're never in this space again. And
that's what we want to dig in hard on.
And if there's for again, for both of
you, if there's one thing that you could
go back and redo, I know everything's
20/20 in hindsight, but injuries aside,
is there one thing that you wish you had
done differently or or anything like
that? Yeah, there's probably a million
things, you know, when you think about
it when you don't have a good season.
So, it's hard to nail it down to one. I
would say looking back, the things that
I'm not pleased with,
um, is our turnover margin and to not
create enough takeaways, not doing a
good enough job with the ball. Those are
the things that come to mind first.
Um,
we want to play bold, we want to play
aggressive, but, uh, that part, um,
you know, you have to more emphasis,
more things in for it. That would be one
that comes to mind first. The one thing,
um,
that there's too many to list. There's
like like paper cuts that would like I
don't know how the saying goes, like
death by a million paper cuts. There's,
you know, like when you're in this
space, you're constantly evaluating and,
okay, where do we go? And
even yesterday, like I had said, I'd
hoped we'd find some of these winning
time moments
before the off season. And so, yesterday
being behind in the fourth quarter,
getting a touchdown, getting a stop,
getting another touchdown, defensive
stop, that's what I was looking for. And
so, to see some of that applied through
the practice, uh, I was pleased to see
it. I thought it was like a step in the
right direction. We're not waiting till
the off season to get this fixed.
Like it has to be addressed and worked
on. And so, I was pleased to see that.
Um, no matter who is in.
Yeah, I I I would echo a lot of what he
said. I think, um,
you know, taking care of the ball, all
doing a better job tackling, um,
but the fundamentals of the of the game
and in our play style, I think slipped a
little bit. But, um, those are things
that we really need to to hit on and
harp, you know, from the very beginning
and and make sure that we're upholding
that standard week in and week out.
Uh, David Aldridge with The Athletic.
Adam,
what do you think needs to be fixed on
this roster?
Uh, fixed, um, you know, I think, you
know, health health played a big part.
Certainly wasn't even close to the only
part, but I think starting with a
healthy team and and really and staying
healthy is is a big deal. Um,
but I I know there's, you know, I think
I think I feel really good at some
spots, but there's certainly a a few
spots where we can improve and and get
young, really, you know, fast, exciting,
explosive talent. And that's what we're
doing right now. We're working on the
draft and got a set of draft meetings
coming up next week, which I'm really,
really excited about. Got the scouts all
showing us their reports and and
identifying some guys. We have a high
pick, which is something that you don't
really want if it's your own pick, but
we're going to take advantage of that
and try to find a young explosive
playmaker, you know, wherever that may
be.
Specifically on the defensive side of
the ball, what are you going to be
looking at and attacking?
Um,
you know, I think there's a lot of spots
that I think where we can we can look
at. I think, um, certainly another pass
rusher would be something we'd
definitely be looking for.
Uh, whether that's, um,
whether that's the draft or free agency.
I think we have a lot of good options in
both of those areas.
Liam Griffin with The Washington Times.
For both of you, I know you're not ready
to address potential coaching or
personnel changes, but when you're
looking at adding coaches or adding
coordinators to the staff, what kind of
traits are you looking to prioritize in
that process?
When you're putting a staff together,
like prior to coming here, Liam, you
wanted to, you know, one is the talent
of the coach, but also the fit. And, uh,
it's not a hell of a lot different than,
you know, like from Adam's side and a
player to adding it to the group, you
know, you've heard us talk about
commanders and it's really no different
on that side. It's it's the fit, it's
the talent. Um, what do they bring
that's unique? And, uh, that's a great
question, man. But, um, to make
communicate, collaborate, um, has unique
skill set to teach. I think that's the
like a number one top of the pile. When
you're teaching, you know, part of this
is why you need to know this specific
skill. This is for the game, for the
coaches that make it come to life. I
think that's what you see when the
players can perform at their best. Um,
so, those are a few of the things.
And for Adam, uh, you guys were the
oldest team in the league by a snap
weighted basis this year and you're
coming into a season with kind of
limited draft capital. So, how do you go
about, you know, returning the 30
pending free agents and getting younger
while trying to maintain a sense of
continuity?
Yeah, I think, um, that's something
that's been talked about a lot and I
think fairly in in a lot of aspects. Um,
but, you know, I I think you're always
trying to get younger and faster and I
think, uh, that'll be a big emphasis for
us this off season.
Go to Tashaun, all right?
I hear the speed coming around the
corner. Tashaun,
What about Tashaun with The Washington
Post?
I know you guys have had a lot of one
and two-year deals in free agency,
specifically, um, your first couple
years here. Um, do you anticipate
getting more aggressive with you guys
having a lot of cap space this off
season? And then, how do you balance
that as a GM of, you know, picking your
spots to go with smaller with deals or
maybe taking some bigger swings in free
agency?
Yeah, I think a a lot of it has to do
with the opportunity and the and the
specific players. Like I think, um, with
with certain players when we when we got
here,
we did a little longer term deal, three
three-year deals. That we haven't done
much more than that except for extending
our own guys. Um,
but I think a lot of it depends on the
player, the opportunity and and just how
the how they fit. You know, there's a
lot of risk, I think,
in free agency if you don't have a ton
of familiarity with that. And,
you know, in the past, you know, places
I've been, the places the the the
biggest mistakes we made were investing
a lot in in a lot of years into a player
you don't really know. So, I think
there's there there's where you carry a
lot of risk in making a big mistake. So,
we'll look at everything individually,
but I do I I don't have I don't think
any of us have
any um aversion for doing the long-term
deals. It just depends on the player and
the situation. Yeah.
With Washington Post. Adam, is there a
way to come up with kind of a long-term
plan to keep Jayden upright and make
sure he plays 15 or 17 games rather than
seven?
Um
Is there a way I I think really I I
think and this might be a better
question for DQ, but you know, from from
me, I think it's just continuing to like
from my, you know, from a personnel or
GM perspective is continuing to put good
players around You know, what that's in
front of him at the O line, it's it's
running backs to to control the ball and
control the clock and not put it all on
his shoulders and get in second and
third and manageables. It's receivers
that he can he can trust and throw to so
that he's not holding on the ball
longer. Um and and so
from my perspective, it's just getting
good players around him, getting a good
defense on the other side so he's not um
it's not all on his shoulders to win the
game. So,
I can DQ can probably talk more
schematically, but in terms of from me,
I think those are the things that that I
can and need to do to help him out.
involved in those discussions of like,
hey, this is how we want you to play,
this is who you, you know, we're
surrounding you with. How Yeah,
absolutely. How much of a part of that
Very much so that part and um even
after, you know,
his injury, we, you know, specifically,
you know,
this is the area. This is what we're
going to work on him. As opposed to
waiting till the off season, we decided
let's get a jump start on that. So, very
much so, um will he be a part of it, but
I would say not only will he, like, we
already are going there. And so, it's
really important. We know what he brings
to us, what he means to us and um
you know, like, I think
it's all-encompassing, you know, in in
how we go play the game. So,
you know, we're like fully committed to,
you know, finding ways to continue to do
that.
Tom Schad with The Washington Post. Um
Adam, I had a couple questions about
Laremy Tunsil, obviously one of the big
off-season additions. How would you
evaluate kind of the impact that he had
on the team? Have you had any talks with
him, early talks, about a contract
extension? And did the situation with
Terry kind of inform how you'll go about
those potential talks?
Yeah, um you know, in in terms of the
evaluation, um I think in his impact on
our team, I thought it was really
outstanding both on the field and in the
locker room. Um
He's a great leader. Uh I don't think
and he's [clears throat] not really up
front about it, but he's he's an
outstanding leader, he's an outstanding
mentor to the other O linemen. He's he's
a really good teammate in in a lot of
ways that you don't really see cuz he's
not looking for attention, but um
really um just it's it's been really
really awesome to get to know him and to
see how he goes about his business.
Incredibly hard worker.
Um and then on the field, I thought, you
know, he was one of the better left
tackles, if not the best in the league.
I don't he didn't get recognition for
the Pro Bowl, uh which I was
disappointed in, but um you look at the
metrics, he did a great job. So,
uh that's all to say that um
you know, we've had, you know, constant
communication. He's self-represented. Uh
but we he has a team around him that
that we have constant communication with
and had throughout the year. So, um I
think what I can say is is we definitely
want to get something done with him and
sooner rather than later.
Scott Abraham, ABC 7. This question is
for both of you. Um
I think the big question fans want to
know here is
how do you go from a team that was one
win away from going to the Super Bowl,
and injuries aside, because every team
goes through injuries.
So, how do you go from a team that was
one win away from going to the Super
Bowl to five wins? Like, what happened?
Like, how can you do some
self-reflection and aside from injuries?
Yeah, we're we're digging that as hard
as we can, Scott, honestly, so we will
never be in this, you know, situation or
have a season like this again. Um so
many factors to say, you know, how do we
play it better, how do we coach it
better, how do we live it better
together. Um the reason that one of the
reasons um that gives us so much um
insight for why we're going to play
excellent football, it's the locker
room. And when you go through, you know,
a terrible season,
you want to see you find out a lot about
guys and
you've been in the locker room, you've
seen how tight and connected these guys
are and how hard they want to fight for
one another. So, in the midst of a
terrible season, I know that part is
right. And if you have that part right,
Scott, then I'm certain, you know,
with the changes, with the things that
we need to do moving forward, um we're
not just trying to be good for one year,
we're trying to do it as good as we can
for a long time. And man, are there
lessons from this season that we're
going to apply in '26, '27, '28 and
beyond. And uh that's what I'd want you
and our our fan base to know that uh
like
man, it was hard and uh hard decisions
have to be made, but uh
I can tell you how many lessons there
are to gain.
Man, it's it's a crazy amount.
Adam, you have anything to add?
Yeah, I mean, I would echo a lot of what
DQ said, but um
you know, obviously there's it's not
just one thing, it's not just the
injuries, it's not just this, it's not
just that. Um but you know, going
through a season like this, which is
terrible and and certainly not even
close to our standard, um like Q said,
that there's a lot of lessons that we
learned and a lot of lessons we'll apply
moving forward in terms of you know,
myself, you know, just the decisions
that I make on a daily basis, the
decisions that we make in terms of our
our roster construction and all those
different things. But we look at
everything and it's a good time to
reflect
We'll have a lot of time this off season
to really dig into all of that. We've
we've looked at a lot throughout the
season, but really kind of get together
and say, what can we do better? And and
that's looking at everything, every
single thing. And Adam, I want to
quickly ask you about the tight end
position. Obviously, Zach's future is
kind of uncertain right now. You're
looking at the tight ends on the roster,
how do you evaluate that and maybe
add another piece uh in terms of a tight
end, free agency draft?
Yeah, the um so, we have I believe three
coming back uh under contract, which is
uh
it's uh Bates, Ben and and Yankoff. Um
Rogers is on the practice squad and then
obviously we lost Zach, which is a was a
big loss. Zach's a
um you know, Hall of Fame caliber player
who's really really excellent in the
pass game. So, I think um
just depending on how Zach comes along
um in coming back, I don't I don't
anticipate him being ready at the
beginning of the season, but um so, you
look into develop and really utilize
those three guys' skill set and I think
they're all really good players in their
own right. Ben's
um developing a lot. He's gotten a lot
better this year and I think he's got
another level to go to. John's one of
the best blocking tight ends in the
league and and Coulson's kind of a jack
of all trades, but an excellent special
teams player for a tight end. So,
uh as you're looking at it right there,
where can you find someone who's, you
know, really really good on third down?
Could it be one of those guys, somebody
who can always get open and the
quarterback can can always rely on? Can
it be one of those guys or are we going
to go outside, whether the draft or free
agency, and get that? So, you know,
think of a Zach Ertz type of skill set
where, you know, Jayden knows where he's
going to be when he's going to be and
trust that he's going to catch the ball
and make the play, which he did uh
really incredibly for the last two
years. And that's sorely missed um for
sure.
Hey guys, JP Finlay, NBC 4, 1067. Adam,
for you, going into this draft with just
two picks Thursday, Friday night, how
does that impact how you approach free
agency, whether it's more aggressive or
or a different approach than perhaps
these last few seasons?
Um
I think you always want to look at the
um the overall landscape with the draft
and free agency and and understand where
the strengths and the weaknesses are and
use those to your advantage in terms of
where you're going to really invest in
one or the other. Obviously,
free agency comes first, you know, and
then you it I wish it was the other way
around where you draft first and you
supplement with free agency. That's
that's not the way it works though. But
with only having, you know, one pick,
like you said, or yeah, what do we have?
Two top 10. Two, yeah, yeah,
sorry. We We don't have a second or a
fourth, which uh
actually very happy that that that
turned out that way with Laremy. I think
I'd I'd do that one all over again, but
um obviously we have a top 10 pick,
which, you know, you could look to move
and and get more picks if the
opportunity arises. Um
but certainly I think every off season,
no matter what your picks are, what you
have, you always trying to maximize both
the draft and free agency. Getting guys
that um you know, you could you might
not be able to get in the other one. So,
if you're going
free agency, it's super heavy at one
position, maybe you go there and then
the draft, you go you go elsewhere to
fill that fill those needs.
Sorry, DQ, that all the questions are
for Adam, but we get to talk to you all
the time.
>> man. Um
You guys talk about your comprehensive
approach a lot. Adam, I'm curious,
what's your role in the coaching staff
decisions?
Uh I'm really just here to support DQ.
The coaching staff is is DQ's and um I'm
always here to help, like, during the
season on and off season, however I can,
you know, to help support him and help
him make the decisions that he needs to
make and and certainly
um where it really wherever he needs.
So, it's not, you know, I'm not involved
in whatever decision it is. It's it's
always DQ's call and and I have his back
on whatever he he to do. There's not
silos here, JP's coaching and scouts, we
connect, we talk a lot, we visit a lot.
And so,
um it's one of the things I I enjoy most
is those conversations. It's different
perspective, different points of view.
So, um it's as collaborative as as I've
been a part of. Yeah.
Good evening, gentlemen. David Harrison,
WUSA9. Um coach, unfortunately, do have
a question for you.
Uh yesterday, Von Miller talked to us
about uh or said a familiar phrase that
you say a lot is is forget next time,
get them this time. And when he
mentioned that, he said that his the
reason he has that saying is cuz it
comes from not playing for yourself.
When you play for yourself, you can get
that sack the next play or you get that
tackle the next time. But when you're
playing for each other, you want to get
it this time. There is no next time. I
mean, how much does that resonate? I
know you have said that phrase. How much
does that resonate with the spirit of
why you say that? Yeah, and uh
it doesn't surprise me that I heard him
say that. Um he has been a remarkable
teammate. Adam was talking about Laremy
and kind of the impact that he's made.
And both of them
are quiet, so confident in their how
they play and their style. Uh it's
almost like they can speak softly, but
you're leaning in. Uh people want to
gain the knowledge and the wisdom that
they have. And I'm super grateful for
both of them because they're wanting to
share that knowledge and that wisdom.
And as a veteran player, you can imagine
the impact that it has on the younger
ones. And even at one when we're calling
younger, I'm saying been in the league a
shorter amount of time. Um
it's very cool to go through. This is
going to happen. You can hear him on the
sideline talking next one we're going to
do this. This play's going to happen.
And so, those are things that come up
that you can't really coach. It comes
with the experience. And there's
advantages with having people like that
on the roster that have wisdom and
impact and they're willing to share it.
Um that's a big deal. And neither Laremy
or
um Von or Wags or Zach or any of them,
we've never had to even conversations
will you take this one under, will you
do that? Cuz that's not like forcing
someone to lead. That's not effective.
They just naturally,
you know, get a way to pay it forward.
And um it's really cool. Uh I've had a
in a really tough season, I've really
enjoyed coaching Von.
And AP, as you get closer to draft
weekend, um is there a point in your
process where as you guys are building
like your top 100 list or however you
you design your board that you get the
coaches involved and kind of say like
hey, we really like this player because
of these traits. How do you think he
would fit into what you're trying to do
as as a coordinator?
Yeah, actually, it kind of plays off
what DQ just said. I mean, we we
collaborate on everything. So, the
coaches are involved with everything we
do in the off season. Very involved. And
um like we went we go through
say a
uh free agency meeting
like a few weeks ago. Well, we'll give
we kind of break it down and give our
list to the coaches. The coaches watch
the the players that we have identified,
so they don't have to watch everybody
cuz they don't have the time to watch
everybody. And then we all meet together
and and we we make those decisions
collaboratively. So, that's the same
with the draft. So, we're not going to
draft players that the coaches don't
like, that don't fit their scheme. And
and we'll really heavily lean to that.
And if we don't understand it, then
we'll we'll sit down together and watch
film and they'll explain why this this
player fits us. And and it really is a
great learning lesson for both of us.
And when we do that, when we get players
that the scouts like and the coaches
like and the analytics like, those are
those are our biggest hit rates. So, I
don't I don't really know any other way
to do it. And and I think I don't think
there's a better way to do it than to
collaborate and make sure that we're all
on the same page and all bought in.
Just recently, the scouts were here on
some meetings and just, you know,
you know, have a team meeting and you
see all them in the back, it kind of
speaks to everybody doing it together.
Everybody's tight in the room. And so,
having the scouts here with the coaches,
with the team, I think that's a perfect
example of how we, you know, kind of
mesh everybody together. Like here I am
looking out at players and coaches and
scouts and, you know, in the team
meeting on Wednesday and Thursday and
Friday as they were, you know, took a
break from their meeting to come into
the team meeting. This is how we're
going to go win this. This is how we're
going to attack it. So, I liked them
being all in our our meetings the week
they were here.
Mitch Tischler, Money Moves Sports. Uh
Dan, for you, um in your head coaching
career, you've kind of done it both ways
where you've been both head coach and DC
or had somebody that you can delegate
to. Is it on the table that next year
you would stay in the same role that you
kind of finished this season or you
think it's better as a head coach to be
able to delegate and kind of be big
picture? Yeah, it's a good question,
Mitch. I think what I've learned is uh
make the best decision for what the team
needs. And uh so, as we're going through
this, man, a lot to gain through these
exit interviews, where we're at. And uh
but that's that's really where I'm at.
I'm not in that space yet. I'm
definitely doing this. I'm definitely
not. What I do know um that I'll be
heavily involved, you know, one way or
another. And
that's part that I do enjoy. But um
yeah, I I think I'll keep an open mind,
you know, as I'm going through the next,
you know, parts of the process.
Having fired a couple different staffs
throughout your career, how do you
balance going after coaches and and
personnel folks that you know versus
guys who might be able to bring in kind
of new ideas, different ideas to a to a
team as a whole? How do you balance kind
of Yeah, I think you want to always have
like a contingency planning system ahead
for when, you know, changes are are
made. And so, you want to think about
those people who are fresh, who's, you
know, on ideas, who's within your own,
you know, building that new status is to
go. And so, you keep that in mind. Um
but you you're always just kind of, you
know, watching and learning and growing.
And you have to adapt. And some of the
things that were effective, you know, 10
years ago, 5 years ago, evolve and
change. And it's kind of one of the fun
parts of coaching. And through the
years, um
I've met some fantastic coaches that I
didn't know before. And you know, one
that left this year was Tavita. And so,
when I got here, he was somebody that I
wanted to hire
um and to be here. And so, man, I'm
super grateful. I learned a lot from
Tavita. And that's just like one small
example amongst others, a Bobby Ingram
or others that um you know, I may not
have known or I've known of them. And
then to actually, you know, go shoulder
to shoulder in couple years, then you
you find out a lot.
Uh Ben Standig with the Team 980 and the
Last Man Standing. Adam, for you, um
with regards to the wide receiver room,
going back to the spring and the summer,
obviously in an ideal world, you
[clears throat] have you have Terry, you
have Dybo, and you have Noah Brown. But,
you have Terry holding out um early on,
Noah gets hurt in
uh mini camp, misses all of training
camp, and both those guys were out. At
what point did did you just look at that
and think we still have enough depth?
Cuz it's from the outside, it seemed to
be
a wonder as to what would happen. And
obviously, those guys were out a lot of
the year.
Yeah, I think um anytime you get your
your top two starting guys, it hurts
your depth regardless of how much depth
you have. Um
certainly, we we're always looking for
you know, for help. We're always looking
to get every room better. Uh we explored
a lot of different way ways to to get
better. We ended up getting Trey Burks,
who ended up being a really good player
for us down down the stretch. Um
But yeah, a lot of it has to do with
opportunity and and one and then what,
you know, what the what the cost is in
in order to do that. And
you know, did not, you know,
I think both Noah's and Terry's injuries
probably were a little bit longer than
we thought they were going to be. And
so, all that played into it. But
certainly, um you know, it made it hard
for Jayden, you know, but with not
having the the full complement of
receivers and uh some young guys behind
him. So, I think that's a good lesson,
for sure. Um but
uh I think uh
you know,
we did explore a lot of different
things. We we just didn't always pull
the trigger just depending on what that
cost or what, you know, whether it's
draft capital, whether it's contract,
whatever it is, you know. And um
you know, I think it's certain certainly
something we'll have to look at down the
road.
And obviously,
the front office is about looking ahead,
the coach is about looking in the
moment. When you guys are in the
position where you're eliminated from
the playoffs or the season's going a
certain way, do you weigh in and say,
"Hey, maybe we need to get some younger
guys in to see what we have next year"
or even have a discussion about, "Hey,
if we win a game in the last week, it
could affect draft status" and the
importance perhaps of that? Even if you
say we're not going to worry about that,
do you weigh in on those matters? I told
him the tank and he just said no. He
didn't No, um
you know, that game was important.
The game was important for us to win, so
I'm really glad we won for for a lot of
different reasons. Um
but in terms of
uh just weighing in on personnel things,
I think, you know, it goes back to what
Q was saying. We talk all the time. We
talk every single day, all day about,
you know, how can we do better? You
know, and I'll make suggestions and I'll
say, "Oh, that's a good idea" or "No,
this is why we we won't do that." But I
think that's in a constant dialogue
between us. And there's no, you know,
it's it's we have a great respect for
each other. So, if I ask a question, he
knows where it's coming from. And it's
not coming from a bad place. It's either
coming from trying to get information or
just understanding. So,
um but yeah, we're always talking about
that, you know, every single week, you
know, regardless of our record, you
know, always trying to
Sometimes I have ideas that I think are
good and they're not. And so, and he'll
tell me why. And and then sometimes they
are they are good. So, I think that's a
healthy relationship that we'll always
have. And I hope that, you know, we'll
we'll continue to have.
Yeah. Time for three more.
I'm messing with you.
Um
Good evening. Candy Waller, Bowie TV. Um
and this is for both of you all. When
you take a look at your draft classes,
so last year and this year,
how well do you think they're doing? Are
they right where you think they would be
right now or have they exceeded
expectations or not so much?
I can start, Candy, on that. Um
I've I visited with a lot of them um
over the last, I don't know, 2 weeks or
so. And I love some of the trajectory
um that some of them are on. The belief
that we have in them is so strong, and
so that's kind of what your first and
second year is. It kind of goes up, but
it goes down. I wish development was
just like going straight up. That would
be awesome.
But what I can say is like we've got
some really really good strong
foundation pieces of what we're building
that are commanders that play it the
right way, and like to see them develop
and grow, like that's one of the things
I love the most about our team and where
they're headed.
Yeah, I I would I would echo that and
just say
um
you know, there there's a lot of really
young players that still have a great
future ahead of them. So, there's guys
that haven't had as many opportunities
as others for whatever reason, and a lot
of times it's cuz there's good players
in front of them, but um we still have a
ton of belief in all of them, and they
all have another, you know, another
level they can go to, every every single
one of them, and they're all willing to
do that. So, very happy with the young
men. Um and like Q said, some some of
them have developed faster, some of had
their ups and downs, and that's okay, we
all do, uh especially when we're first
starting something, and but in terms of
all that, I have a ton of belief in all
those guys.
Donna Hopkins, Pro Football Plus. This
is for both of you all. Uh when you look
at depth across the team this year, do
you feel like in each area you had it,
and if not, what do you think you need
at most in preparing for 2026?
Yeah, Donna, it's a good question. It's
um
you're something that you're thinking
about constantly, and even as that
shifts, like um offensive line, we
really had our most depth,
um and even that was challenged um here
at the end of the season with some
different roster change-up. So,
with the addition of the practice squad
and allowing that to be that
that is a bigger piece than it's ever
been, and some veterans, some not, but
developing within is a really big piece.
Um
we'll continue to dig in hard on that as
development coaches, that's our job to
take them to the next spot, take them to
the next level, and we're just talking
about some of the players that we have
so much belief in. It is helping them
get to that next spot, and so
um as depth goes, um
you got to dig in, you got to find where
are you vulnerable, where do you got to
keep developing people, you know, what
would be the contingency plan if this
happened this week. So, that's really
where like the start of the week goes
with Adam and I on Monday after we get
done through the injury report, what
would change, what would be the same,
and uh this year we had far too many of
those conversations about this is how
we're going to go, and this is how we'll
play it. But
you know, what also came from that, some
guys that maybe we wouldn't have known
as much about, and uh how would it go,
and what it would look like, and so when
called upon, how would they deliver, and
uh
you know, as we're going through it,
it's uh it's difficult at times, but um
having that depth piece is a big deal,
and it's developmental, it's taking
people to the next space most often.
Yeah, it it was certainly challenged our
depth this whole year, and um
you know, I really first I would say
just great job by our personnel staff
because every every Monday was was, you
know, a a challenge in getting the guys
in that we could just to get just to
play. Um but then certainly you got to
think about where do you have depth for
guys that are ready to play and and
contribute, or are you using that depth
for guys on the practice squad that you
want to develop and and continue to they
may not be quite ready to play yet, and
so you know, learning to find that
balance in at every position is
something we're we're we're always
constantly trying to get better at. Um
but yeah, we were certainly challenged
this year, and and I think um you know,
finding the balance of
getting enough players that when you're
really decimated at a position to get
out and and get you out of a game till
those guys get back, that's uh certainly
something we're going to look into.
Hey guys.
Hey guys, Zach Perelis, CBS Sports. Uh
this is for Adam. This is going back a
couple years for you, but you were with
the 49ers in kind of an eerily similar
spot where you had a breakthrough year,
then next year there were some injuries
kind of across the board, kind of fell
back, and then you guys got right back
to it. Does this situation remind you at
all of that one, and what lessons did
you learn of being able to build and
have that roster right back after kind
of that one down year following the
breakthrough?
Yeah, first of all, I hope so. I hope
so. Hope that happens. Um
you know, and those those things, I
mean, that I I remember that year
vividly, and it it's a nightmare, you
know, when you have these certain games
like we had in Green Bay, or we had that
in that year in New York where we just
it was like carnage, and you know, it's
it's really hard to bounce back. Um
but I think, you know, the lessons are
you know, you look into everything, you
look into, you know, why the guys got
hurt. Sometimes they got hurt because
it's just a freak injury, sometimes they
got hurt because we didn't do a good
good enough job loan managing or or
getting them warmed up or whatever it
is. So, you you can look into all that.
Um I have great belief in our health and
performance team. They do a really good
job. They have a ton of care for our
players, and and really appreciate that.
Um but you look into that, you look
into, you know, the type of players you
bring in, their injury histories moving
forward, you really dig into that. You
know, a lot of the times, um
you know, the the past injury history
dictates kind of their future injury
history. So, so that's that's a big
piece of it, but really um
what I'm proud of this year, and I think
that year as well, that was a little
more challenging because uh uh it was a
COVID year, and we ended up having to
move to Arizona for a month, but it
really tests your resolve, and it tests
your what we call brotherhood. And um
what was cool to see today, we we met
with a lot of players today in the
check-out process, and um you know,
really tip my cap to cap to DQ here cuz
a lot of them, despite the
the the poor results, everybody really
still believed in in us and this team
and what we're doing and the direction
we're going. So, I think that's
something that you can really lean on
and say, "Okay, we can dig into this
more and and, you know, bank on that
we're going to have a little bit better
luck with that next year and and
continue to add healthy pieces and get
those guys that we lost back, which is a
big deal, too. We get a lot of those
guys back, which will really make us
look a lot different.
All right. Thanks, guys. Appreciate it.
All right. Thanks, everybody. Thanks,
everybody.
>> [clears throat]
>> What was that?